♪ Here we are going far ♪
♪ to save all that we love ♪
♪ If we give all we've got ♪
♪ we will make it through ♪
♪ Here we are like a star ♪
♪ shining bright on your world today ♪
♪ Make evil go away ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we'll reset it all ♪
♪ Code Lyoko be there when you call ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we will stand real tall ♪
♪ Code Lyoko stronger after all ♪
Please let me get a good grade, please let me get a good grade,
just for once, I’m begging you, please let me get a good grade.
You know, you might have better luck if you studied before an exam.1:18
It beats praying for them.
Excellent work Herb, I’m not surprised either, I gave you an A- as usual,
the minus to show you can always improve. Well done.
Thank you, sir.
I don’t get it, how can such a good student be such a nerd?
But then again, you did crush Jeremie who’s even nerdier than you are.
Keeping with the time-honored tradition,
I uh, I’ve saved the best paper for last.
I’m the only one left.
He did just say the best, didn’t he, huh?
I hate to burst your bubble, but it sounded like sarcasm.
Ulrich Stern. There were so many spelling errors in this assignment that
at first I thought it was written in some obscure and primitive language.
But no, in fact, it was in English, unfortunately. I’ve given you an F+,
the plus to get you room to do worse next time.
That wasn’t just sarcastic, it was bombastic.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Come in. Ah, Ms. Ishiyama.
Well, I must say I’m flattered that you answered my request to come and see me.
Given your constant lateness and repeated absences over these past few weeks,
I’m just flabbergasted that you actually decided to show up.
To what do I owe this great honor?
I’m sorry, sir, I really am.
Perhaps, but not as much as I am.
I’m sincerely sorry to have to say this to you Yumi,
but unfortunately you don’t leave me any choice.
If I here that you are absent or late just one more time,
I shall be forced to expel you from the academy.
Expulsion? You’re kidding!
Oh no, Delmas was dead serious this time.
This can’t go on much longer.
It’s getting harder and harder to keep up with our school work and fight against Xana.
Better believe it, Einstein.
If you ask me, Xana’s trying to wear us down.
Well there is one thing we can do.
If we could recruit one more Lyoko Warrior,
it would give us some breathing room.
And who did you have in mind?
There’s William. He’s already shown us what he can do.
No way, we’ve already been over this,
William’s too much of a hothead. No, he can’t be trusted.
As far as I’m concerned, Aelita’s right, it’s a good idea.
No, it’s a very bad idea.
Look, we’re all really tired. We don’t we talk about this tomorrow?
Let’s take advantage of the fact that Xana hasn’t attacked and get a good night’s sleep.
I’ll stay up a little while and work a way to virtualize you directly into Sector Five.
Okay guys? I’ve got some calculations to do.
That’s what you call getting some sleep, Jeremie?
I don’t need all that much sleep
and besides, I’ll sleep a lot better once we defeat Xana.
We all will, Aelita. Not before.
Aelita, I have to talk to you!
What are you so excited about?
I did it! I finally found a way to virtualiz--
-- all of you into Sector Five directly.
We have to run a test right now.
Come on, let’s go to the computer lab.
But we have a physics test this morning.
You and I have fabulous grades Aelita.
We can afford to skip one exam.
I don’t think we should.
Besides, we have to tell the others.
No, no way we’re skipping the exam.
I need a decent grade to bring up my average.
Ulrich’s right, what’s more, if we’re all absent,
they’re bound to suspect something.
And I’m sure to get expelled.
Some adventurers you are.
Don’t be like that.
We’ll go after the test is over, Jeremie, at lunch time.
Okay, go ahead. I’ll meet you in the lunchroom.
I have to go back and get some stuff.
Oh no…
Hey, Jeremie, what’s the answer to question number one?
Is Aelita done yet?
How should I know?
Ask her.
Aelita, Jeremie wants to know if you’re finished yet.
Huh?
Odd? Would you like me to give you some help?
Oh gee, thanks Mrs. Hertz,
I sure could use a little.
I’ve had quite enough of watching you--
--copy answers left and right, Odd.
But ma’am, no I was just-
Jeremie, have you completed the exam?
Yes ma’am.
Good, well then you will please escort your classmate to the principal’s office.
It’s time Odd was punished.
Why wouldn’t you let me copy off you this time?
We wouldn't be here now.
And if you studied like everyone else,
we wouldn’t be here now.
Look, A) not everyone else studies, and B) I am not like everyone else,
I’m special, unique. Like you, by the way.
(PHONE RINGING)
Huh?
Hello?
Odd, it’s me, Jeremie.
Hm, today isn’t April Fools day.
Odd, listen to me,
Xana has created a clone of me from a polymorphic spectre.
We fought at the factory
and he tried to drown me. But I survived.
I don’t know what he’s planning, but-
Who’s that?
You wouldn’t believe me if I told you.
He’s right next to you, isn’t he?
Uh, well yeah, I mean I don’t know.
Look in his eyes Odd.
Can you see the sign of Xana?
Uh...
You didn’t answer me, who is it?
J-J-J-Jeremy, I think you’re right, what do I do now, huh?
(ELECTRICAL CRACKLING)
Nothing. There’s nothing you can do.
Odd? Odd! What’s going on?
Answer me will you? Odd!
May I remind each of you not to spend too much time in the dark room printing your photos.
Since the dark room is for everyone to share. It’s nobody’s personal dark room.
I remember when I was a war photographer.
We had to develop our prints fast while bombs were falling.
You were a war photographer, huh, Jim?
Yeah, but I’d rather not talk about it.
Okay, Yumi and William, you’re the first up.
You know, I had another dream about you last night.
Is that so?
There was this giant computer in this huge room like a factory,
you know? And then, both you and I were on this bridge--
--fighting against some factory worker who was doing these wild acrobatics.
You really dreamed that?
Yeah. I’ve been having that same dream for a really long time.
It’s totally weird. Then again, of course,
it’s only a dream, and they’re always a little bit weird.
Right, shall we go?
(PHONE RINGING)
Jeremie, what’s going on?
This light means that your classmates have started the developing. When you see that,
absolutely no one should open the door. The light would ruin the pictures.
Listen Jeremie, if I skip class one more time,
I’ll be expelled, you get it, what do we do then?
I don’t know what’s going on, but you but you can always get out through there.
And Jim?
Leave it to me. I’ll take care of Jim.
He won’t notice a thing. Just don’t be too long, that’s all.
But why would you do that for me?
Let’s just say that in my dream, I really enjoyed helping you out,
so why not try it in real life? Might be just as much fun.
Okay Jeremie, I’m coming.
Great. Find Odd and go get Ulrich and Aelita.
I’m going to need all of you to deactivate the tower that my evil twin set up.
Speaking of whom, I wonder where he could be right now?
Jeremie, I found Odd. He’s a little woozy, but he’s okay.
We’re gonna try to get Aelita and Ulrich and then we’ll meet you.
Okay, but hurry up.
I’ll start setting up your transfer to Lyoko.
Hm, well what do you know,
you actually survived.
Huh?
You’re a real swimming champ.
I’m almost proud to resemble you, I really am.
With the exception that I am far more powerful than you.
(SCREAMING)
(PHONE RINGING)
Ulrich, we have to go.
It looks like there’s an emergency.
Sorry, emergency or not, I’m not moving.
I need the grade, and this time I’m off to a decent start.
Okay, but I’d better go.
Meet up with us when you’ve finished.
Mh hm.
(SCREAMING)
Hm, what are they doing in there?
What’s taking so long? Yumi, William, come on!
We’re almost done Jim! Wait till you see the prints! They’re fantastic!
Taken long enough. I’d like to see them,
so hurry it up, will you?
Believe me Jim,
we’re going as fast as we can.
So what does Jeremie’s evil twin look like?
Well, just like Einstein, except with muscles and super powers.
Where’s Ulrich?
He’ll be here as soon as he finishes his exam.
Okay, get down to the scanners on the double, huh?
I’ll start up your transfer.
Where did your nasty twin go?
I have no idea but the faster we deactivate the tower,
the faster we’ll be rid of him.
He’s right, let’s get going.
Odd, what are you waiting for? Let’s go.
Okay, okay, let’s go then.
Alright, time is almost up.
Ah, one more minute.
I’m just not sure.
I should have looked him in the eye, you never know.
I’m sure it was him, aren’t you Aelita?
Uh huh.
Female intuition, you can trust our flair.
If you say so.
Are you ready?
I’ll transfer you as close as I can to the activated tower.
I’m starting up the process.
Scanner, Yumi. Scanner, Aelita. Scanner, Odd.
Virtualization.
Okay Jeremie, bring on our vehicles,
we’re raring to go over here.
Sorry Odd, but I have another plan.
Huh?
Such a great plan plan,
that you guys are gonna just flip out.
We’ve been had by Jeremie’s twin.
Nothing like female intuition, huh, girls?
Oh no, what’s he gonna do?
You want a little male intuition?
Something very nasty.
(LAUGHING)
Huh?
What’s happening to us?
He’s bugged you up.
But why us and not you?
There’s your answer, look!
Huh?
William, Yumi, that’s it, you hear now? Open up!
Can’t Jim, we’re working on the contrast. You know how important the contrast is.
I mean, you know better than we do, if we open up now we’ll lose everything.
Hey Yumi, why do you leave all the talking to William?
Yumi, answer me.
I’m right here Jim. I guarantee you it’ll be worth waiting for.
William and I are making some incredibly beautiful photographs.
Uh, okay. But hurry it up will you?
We will Jim!
Laser arrow!
Huh?
Oh no, it didn’t work!
At this rate, there isn’t gonna be any winner.
Go on, knock yourselves out.
Oh no, Aelita!
We can’t do anything bugged up like this.
Aelita, go on, you’ve gotta defend yourself.
It’s horrible not being able to do anything!
Now she’s gonna make a dash for the way tower.
This can’t be!
And given the circumstances,
there’s not much we can do.
I take back what I said, you’re not even half as smart as me.
As a matter of fact, you’re a stupid dope.
(LAUGHING)
Sorry, but one of us is going to have to go.
Right, and I think that’s gonna have to be you.
Hey, I think I need glasses, I’m seeing double.
Thanks, Ulrich, you got here just in time.
What’s going on on Lyoko?
I wish I knew.
Odd, Yumi?
Jeremie, is that you? For real?
Yes.
I can vouch for that, it’s him alright.
How’s it going for you over there?
Well, you could say that we’re all bugged up.
And a little ridiculous too.
Okay, I’ll take care of that.
Hurry, Aelita is under Xana’s spell,
and she’s heading for the way tower.
We could lose the Mountain sector.
Don’t panic, I’m sending you Ulrich as backup.
Uh, sorry, major problem.
This might take a little more time.
(LAUGHING)
I’m starting up the debugging.
I sure hope this is gonna work.
You’re the main man, Einstein!
Thanks. Now go catch Aelita before she enters the Xana code.
I’m bringing up your vehicles.
Here we go!
It’s great to have my svelte body back!
(GIGGLE)
Things are heating up over here, better hurry.
We’re on it. Where’s Aelita?
Almost at the tower but you can still catch her.
Go on, Yumi, I’ll cover you.
Okay.
Yahoo!
(LAUGHING)
(SCREAMING)
I hope it’s not gonna be too late.
Aelita!
No!
Oh, Jeremie.
There was nothing I could do.
Jeremie, we’re going to lose the Mountain sector.
Don’t forget to bring Aelita and me in.
Jeremie, now’s the time.
(SCREAMING)
I’m gonna rematerialize you.
You okay?
No…
The Mountain sector has completely disappeared.
There’s no way of getting into Sector Five now.
Now Xana can attack the core of Lyoko at any time
and destroy it for good and there’ll be nothing we can do against him.
Lyoko is gone for good and without it,
there’s not a thing we can do to fight Xana.
Hm.
Wait a minute,
these are the results of the calculations I made this morning.
What about them?
Hm. I think I may have found a way to--
--virtualize you directly into Sector Five at last.
You mean the struggle against Xana goes on?
He’s not rid of us yet.
If that’s the case, then we’re gonna need somebody else.
After what’s happened, we don’t have a choice, it seems.
What? I changed my mind. So?
Mh hm.
Hey, right now, you hear? William and Yumi,
I’m gonna open up this door and don’t think I can’t do it.
I used to be a safe cracker. I mean a locksmith- Oof!
Aw, we told you not to come in Jim, now you’ve ruined my pictures. I mean our pictures.
Yumi? Where’s Yumi?
Here I am, Jim.
That’s so uncool for our prints,
we worked really hard on them.
So then, you’re saying my dream really wasn’t a dream?
Right.
It really happened? Are you sure?
I am.
And you’re also sure that you need my help?
You think he’ll say yes?
Of course, if Yumi asked him to dive off a cliff,
he’d do it in a second.
By the way,
how did your physics test go?
Hey, it went really well.
Who’d have thought that studying for a test would help.
Ulrich turning into a good student for once,
William turning into a Lyoko Warrior…
Our little group is going through a lot of pretty huge changes.
Mh hm.
CLOSED CAPTIONING PROVIDED BY THE FOXTROT FANATICS